// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "FIND THE CORRECT ANSWER",
    answer: "D) That's a proud little beige British bulldog",
    options: [
      "A) That's a little beige British proud bulldog",
      "B) That's a proud beige little British bulldog",
      "C) That's a little proud beige British bulldog",
      "D) That's a proud little beige British bulldog",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "I wish I ..... a car, I'm tired of catching the bus.",
    answer: "B) had",
    options: [
      "A) have",
      "B) had",
      "C) would have",
      "D) had had",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Peter can eat ..... as twenty oranges in one sitting.",
    answer: "C) as many",
    options: [
      "A) so many",
      "B) so much",
      "C) as many",
      "D) as much",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "I know he didn't thank you, but he .... have done so.",
    answer: "A) should",
    options: [
      "A) should",
      "B) may",
      "C) must",
      "D) would",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "I won't go to the cinema ..... you come with me.",
    answer: "C) unless",
    options: [
      "A) except",
      "B) otherwise",
      "C) unless",
      "D) therefore",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "He wrote the letter ..... , he didn't need anybody's help.",
    answer: "A) on his own",
    options: [
      "A) on his own",
      "B) by his own",
      "C) on himself",
      "D) by his ownership",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Hotel rooms must be ..... by noon.",
    answer: "A) vacated",
    options: [
      "A) vacated",
      "B) evacuated",
      "C) abandoned",
      "D) leave",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "You can take the book with you ..... you give it back.",
    answer: "D) as long as",
    options: [
      "A) as well as",
      "B) as time as",
      "C) as far as",
      "D) as long as",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Let's go watch the game, .....",
    answer: "B) shall we?",
    options: [
      "A) will we?",
      "B) shall we?",
      "C) let us?",
      "D) don't we?",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "After many years of research, they found the solution .....",
    answer: "B) at last",
    options: [
      "A) at the end",
      "B) at last",
      "C) by the end",
      "D) on the end",
    ]
  },

];